Способы связаться

+77710721672 (Mobile) nurgissa.22@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/itkarinov (LinkedIn)

Основные навыки

Разработка клиентской стороны React.js JavaScript

Certifications

Introduction to Computer Science

Nurgissa Itkarinov

Nurgissa Itkarinov | Junior Frontend Developer in Astana, KZ Нур-Султан, Казахстан

Общие сведения

Since 2022, I have been passionate about learning JavaScript programming languages. I am studying programming, web development, writing websites in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript.

In November 2022 started learning at nFactorial School to Fullstack Junior Frontend Developer.

Looking for a frontend developer job offers.

С 2022 года я занимаюсь изучением языков программирования JavaScript. Я изучаю программирование, веб-разработку, написание сайтов на HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React.

В ноябре 2022 года начал обучение в nFactorial School на Full stack Junior Frontend Developer.

Ищу вакансию фронтенд-разработчика.

Опыт работы

BI Group - строительный холдинг Казахстана 5 лет 10 месяцев

Planning Engineer января 2021 - Present (2 года 2 месяца) Nur-Sultan. Kazakhstan

Involved in the position of Planning Engineer at the Engineering Center of BI Construction & Engineering. Design of infrastructure facilities, public and industrial buildings and structures.

Implementation of control over the timing of the development of design and estimate documentation for the company's projects on construction constructs, control of the readiness of initial permits and verification of compliance with the required standards.

I carry out the collection of the necessary technical documentation necessary for the work on the development of plans.

On behalf of the immediate supervisor, I carry out the development of individual sections of the plan, perform calculations and justifications for them.

I take part in the development of measures for the efficient use of the resources of the design organization.

Control of management documentation regarding the project in accordance with project management standards.

I am developing plans for the need for human resources to achieve a plan for issuing design and estimate documentation for a construction site.

Process Equipment Engineer июля 2020 - декабря 2020 (6 месяцев) Kyzylorda, Kazakhstan

Working as Process Equipment Engineer. Work on the construction of prefabricated hospitals COVID-19.

Selection of equipment for equipping hospitals, furniture, special devices and medical equipment. Participation in the design, acceptance, placement, connection and commissioning of process equipment.

Manager Project Management мая 2017 - июля 2020 (3 года 3 месяца) Nur-Sultan, Kazakhstan

- 1. Data collection for design work.
- 2. Analysis of information on projects.
- 3. Development of the concept of the project.
- 4. Formation and organization of the work of the project management group.
- 5. Acceptance and approval of all decisions on the project.
- 6. Change management in the project.
- 7. Collection, consolidation and analysis of information from projects.
- 8. Participation in the implementation and development of information systems, development of project management methodology.

Bazis Construction Company
Technical Department Engineer
марта 2016 - мая 2017 (1 год 3 месяца)

Nur-Sultan, Kazakhstan

Senior Engineer at Technical Department

Control of the work performed by the contractor in sections: Power supply and lighting, low-voltage networks, Dispatching and automation, Fire alarm

Checking forms from construction teams and subcontractors. Complete set of executive documentation. Monitoring of certificates for building materials. Keeping a limit fence card.

Calculation of units and materials for the project. Calculation of the budget for the construction of the facility. Provision of construction site design and estimate documentation. Consulting on related issues.

Kulager Construction Company Technical Department Engineer июня 2015 - марта 2016 (10 месяцев) Nur-Sultan, Kazakhstan

Keeping a limit fence card. Submission and preparation of applications for building materials. Write-off of M-29 forms from subcontractors. Calculation of materials according to project documentation. Maintenance of material accounting on the object. Calculation of volumes and materials for the project. Calculation of the budget for the construction of the facility. Checking forms KS-3 and F-2 from construction teams and subcontractors. Provision of construction site design and estimate documentation. Consulting on related issues

Bazis Construction Company 1 год 2 месяца Technical Department Engineer апреля 2015 - июня 2015 (3 месяца) Nur-Sultan, Kazakhstan

Work during the summer holidays after the 4th year of study.

Keeping a limit fence card. Submission and preparation of applications for building materials. Write-off of M-29 forms from subcontractors. Calculation of materials according to project documentation. Maintenance of material accounting on the object. Calculation of volumes and materials for the project. Calculation of the budget for the construction of the facility. Checking forms

KS-3 and F-2 from construction teams and subcontractors. Provision of construction site design and estimate documentation. Consulting on related issues

Cost Engineer мая 2014 - апреля 2015 (1 год) Nur-Sultan, Kazakhstan

Work during the summer holidays after the 3rd year of study.

Cost Engineer at Cost Control Department

Bazis Construction Company Standardization and Certification Engineer июня 2013 - августа 2013 (3 месяца) Nur-Sultan, Kazakhstan

Work during the summer holidays after the 2nd year of study.

Standardization and Certification Engineer

Responsibilities: Maintaining and filling out a database of construction acts, checking certificates and passports for building materials, checking the conformity of the quality of building materials, reviewing forms-estimators of work performed from subcontractors and allowing them to be transferred to Technical Department.

Achievements: Expansion of knowledge of filling acts of hidden works for engineering, finishing, monolithic and other works, expansion of knowledge of technological processes in construction, acquisition of knowledge regarding project documentation.

ТОО «Системы безопасности-НС» Low-Voltage Systems Engineer мая 2012 - августа 2012 (4 месяца)

Nur-Sultan, Kazakhstan

Work during the summer holidays after the 1st year of study.

Low-Voltage Systems Engineer

Responsibilities: Installation of cable networks of low-voltage systems.

Achievements: Obtaining knowledge of laying cables for telecommunication, low-voltage networks, expanding knowledge of the materials to be laid for low-current systems

Образование

nFactorial School

Fullstack Junior Frontend Developer, Computer Programming · (ноября 2022 - апреля 2023)

IPMA Kazakhstan

Специалист, Управление проектами ІРМА · (января 2018 - марта 2018)

PMSOFT-Ukraine

Специалист, Project Management in Primavera P6 Prefessional · (января 2017 - марта 2017)

Костанайский Государственный Университет им.

А.Байтурсынова

Бакалавр, Электроэнергетика · (сентября 2011 - мая 2015)